vuaq.com 2011-11-23

# Education Online » Privacy Policy

## Copyright

The material on this website – including pages, documents, graphics, audio and video – is protected by Crown copyright and is subject to the copyright laws of New Zealand and, through international treaties, other countries. The copyright is owned by the New Zealand Ministry of Education (unless the content is identified as being the property of another party).

### For material copyright to the Ministry of Education

You may utilise any of the material on this website that is copyright to the New Zealand Ministry of Education free of charge and without the permission of the Ministry of Education, provided:

  * you are using the material for non-commercial purposes
  * the material is not altered; and
  * the source and copyright owner of the material is acknowledged.

### For material with third party copyright

The permission to reproduce material on this site that is protected by Crown copyright does not extend to any material that is identified as being copyright to a third party. Permission to reproduce such material must be obtained from the copyright holders. This includes material on websites you access via links from this site.

## Disclaimer

This site contains information obtained from within the New Zealand Ministry of Education, and from sources commissioned by the ministry, and is subject to change without notice. The ministry endeavours to the best of its ability to ensure that the information is true, accurate and current. However, the ministry does not accept any liability for the accuracy or content of this information.

## Links to third party websites

The Ministry of Education does not accept any liability for the accuracy or content of information on this website belonging to third parties, nor for the accuracy or content of any third-party website that you may access via a hyperlink from this site. Links to other websites from this one should not be taken as endorsement of those sites or of products offered on those sites.  
When visiting other websites, please refer to the conditions of use and copyright policies of those sites.

### Links from other sites to this one

You are welcome to create a hyperlink to this site from another website. However, this link must not be presented on your site in any context that implies that this website has an association with your site, or endorses your site or product. The Ministry of Education logo may not be used on your site without the ministry’s permission.

## Privacy statement

This privacy notice applies to personal and other information collected on the Ministry of Education’s website: www.vuaq.com

If you voluntarily provide personal information on this website (eg, through email feedback or online forms), we will keep that personal information secure and will not disclose it to any third party. We will only use that information to communicate with you in the way indicated.

If you want to check personal information that we hold, please write to:

The Privacy Officer  
1320 INGLESIDE AVE  
MCLEAN    VA

## Cookies

Browser cookies are small files that are sent by a website and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are used by this website to provide the Ministry of Education with information about site usage and to help us improve our website.

Cookies from this site are not used to gather any personally identifiable information. The information we collect includes the date and time you visited the site, your IP address, the pages you accessed on our site, the search terms you used, details about your operating system (e.g., Windows XP, Mac OSX) and your web browser (eg, Firefox or Internet Explorer).

The data is collected and aggregated for the Ministry of Education by Google Analytics, a measurement and research service.

You can manually disable cookies at any time – check your browser’s ‘Help’ to find out how. This will not affect your ability to view the site.

## Unsolicited email

Publication of email addresses on this site should not be taken as deemed consent to receiving unsolicited email. Persons or organisations wishing to send email material to individuals or organisations whose email addresses appear on this website must comply with the requirements of the [**Unsolicited Electronic Messages Act 2007**](http://www.dia.govt.nz/diawebsite.nsf/wpg_URL/Services-Anti-Spam-Index?OpenDocument&ExpandView#three) (Department of Internal Affairs’ website).
